(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
(This drama is a work of fiction.)
(All characters, organizations,
and events in this drama are fictitious.)
(Scenes with child actors
followed production guidelines.)
Please reconsider, Mr. Seong.
We have nothing right now.
My name is Seong Tae Hun.
I fought my way here
by taking on one guy at a time.
For the past 25 years,
I bet my entire life...
on this.
Mr. Seong.
(Director's Office)
Napa cabbage.
I...
Hey, Mr. Seong.
I was just climbing over
Cheonwang Peak on Jirisan.
At this rate, my heart's going
to hike to heaven before I do.
I told you already, sir.
This napa cabbage...
The raw ingredient, napa cabbage,
is the problem.
Every time, the origin
of the main ingredient changes,
so the taste of our kimchi
changes completely.
So how are we supposed to build
loyal customers?
Right.
So when we think of napa cabbage,
who comes to mind?
Pardon?
You, the napa cabbage expert,
are right here.
I forgot about that.
Then it's settled.
So you'll review the sourcing issue again?
Of course.
You'll do anything for
Mat Story's napa cabbage, right?
Of course, sir.
I've spent over 20 years
researching napa cabbage at Mat Story.
I'll do whatever it takes
to solve this sourcing issue.
The napa cabbage
that you've been dreaming of...
I...
I'll make sure you get it.
Then this time,
please make sure you solve it.
Please work hard on it.
Work hard?
You're the one who'll be doing
all the hard work.
The real...
hard work.
(Jeongseong Kimchi, Baekseonjang Kimchi)
I miss you, Daddy.
You worked very hard today, honey.
It must be morning
in Toronto right now, right?
(Mat Story)
My goodness.
Look at the HR announcement.
Next Monday?
Wow. That's really sudden.
This is what happens
when you don't have connections.
So where is this Yeonri-ri branch?
Don't you know?
They call it a branch,
but it's basically exile.
I'll be getting off here.
Sure.
- I'm sorry.
Sure. Be sorry.
(Seong Tae Hun
New Business Department Manager)
(Transfer Order to Yeonri-ri)
(Director's Office)
Let's not just talk about golf.
Mr. Seong.
I was just about to call you in
to congratulate you.
Mr. Choi.
Members of the board.
This is the man leading
the napa cabbage revolution.
Manager Seong Tae Hun
of the Yeonri-ri Branch.
Let me tell you about this man.
"I will do anything for the company."
Thanks to him,
and his willingness
to work hard for Mat Story,
I was able to make
this wonderful decision today.
Everyone.
Please give a round of applause
for Mr. Seong.
He's factory staff now?
Sounds great.
Mr. Choi.
Could I speak with you?
What is it, Mr. Seong?
Is there a problem?
Mr. Choi. Yeonri-ri?
This...
isn't right.
Isn't this what you wanted?
You said napa cabbage was important.
If the inconsistent suppliers
are the problem,
then we should just...
create our own exclusive source
to ensure consistency.
But...
Mr. Choi.
You're not sending me to Gyeonggi-do
where there's a smart farm.
You're sending me to Yeonri-ri,
where there isn't even a research team.
I know what that means.
Come on. If you know...
Pardon?
The company needs you there.
Are you refusing to go?
Are you going to resign?
I...
I'm giving you a great opportunity here.
Whether you take it,
or not...
That's up to you.
But...
Sir...
(Resignation Letter)
Ji Cheon...
He has to finish med school
and open a clinic.
Ji Sang and Ji Gu in Toronto...
still have to finish their studies.
And you still call yourself
the head of this family?
Did you even think about us?
Do you want us all to end up
on the street?
What have I done?
What?
It's okay.
Yes.
I gave my 20 years to Mat Story.
Even if I hate it, I'll do it again.
I, Seong Tae Hun, won't go down like this.
(EP 1 - Was I Meant to Become a Farmer?)
What am I doing here?
What came over me?
Have I lost my mind?
Why did I say something
I didn't have to say?
You idiot.
Wait a minute.
Isn't this what you wanted?
You said napa cabbage was important.
Wait a minute. Stop.
Then I'll just prove it.
Seong Tae Hun napa cabbage.
Wasn't I going to do this before
retiring anyway?
(Mat Story Yeonri-ri Branch)
This place is a dump. Darn it.
Napa cabbage and people have
something in common.
There are people that you just know...
you shouldn't mess with.
the moment you meet them.
(Yeonri-ri)
A crime-free village.
This is Yeonri-ri.
Welcome.
Are you from Seoul?
What are you doing here on this hot day?
Oh. I'm from Mat Story.
Mat Story?
What's this now?
Pardon?
You got transferred here?
Yes.
Are you a resident here?
I'm the village chief here.
The village chief.
I'm looking for a place to stay nearby.
Which real estate office should I go to?
You're incredibly lucky...
to have run into me at the perfect time.
Nothing works in this village without me.
(Yeonri-ri)
I'm moving here by myself,
so I don't need a big place.
Your wife must be thrilled.
Seeing each other only on weekends
is a blessing, right?
My wife and kids are overseas.
You're a free bird.
You flew and ended up here?
Yeah.
I guess you are taking a break
for a little bit.
Who knows?
You might go back up to Seoul soon.
Would you like to start with that house?
You don't see yards like this
in Seoul, right?
Are you sure this is a yard?
This house is...
No thanks.
I don't think you can call this a house.
These days, everything is full option.
Did you look thoroughly?
Yes, full option.
But it's more like negative features?
Are you sure you came to live here?
Maybe you didn't come to live here.
This house has
the highest ceiling in Yeonri-ri.
Yes, according to your standards.
My standards?
You're tall.
It's so hot.
How long are you going to keep looking?
It's nice and clean, right?
Those chickens are a bonus.
I'm not eating chicken starting today.
This is the last house.
They're all in about the same condition.
But this is the best one so far.
Can we sign a contract today?
I'll ask.
He likes Man Sik's place.
This is the best one so far.
What?
- Really? All right.
- There's no time.
Gosh. I'm sorry.
There's a lien on the house,
so it can't be rented.
It looks like someone
caused trouble again.
I have an appointment today
that I must get to.
Then...
what about this house?
Yes, that one is available.
I need to get back now.
Get going.
- Thank you. Thank you.
- Good-bye.
- You know the way out?
- Yes.
Look at him go.
Mat Story?
Goodness. It's so hot.
If the executive director wants to see me,
that means it's not over yet.
Let's tough it out.
Even if I have to grind myself down
like cabbage filling.
You can do it, Seong Tae Hun.
Come in.
Did you want to see me?
About the Yeonri-ri transfer...
I know that people are gossiping.
"They sent him to a dead-end post
because he's without connections."
"It's a trick to push him out."
Is that what you think, too?
Sir.
Please reconsider the Yeonri-ri transfer.
Yes?
Not at all, sir.
I already found a place
to stay in Yeonri-ri today.
Good. That's the attitude.
So you have three kids?
Two are studying in Canada,
and your eldest is in medical school?
It must be costing you a fortune.
How did you know?
All fathers in Korea live the same life.
What you'll be doing in Yeonri-ri...
is much bigger than you think.
It's a mission that the future of
Mat Story depends on.
So if I successfully grow
Mat Story napa cabbage,
does that mean I can return
to headquarters?
Mr. Seong Tae Hun.
Go to Yeonri-ri,
and prove your value.
Yes, sir.
I...
will make a comeback to Seoul.
Right in the middle of this building,
I'll put up a napa cabbage statue,
and my kids,
and my wife...
will applaud me as I retire.
I will do it.
(Wife)
Honey.
Well...
I was just about to call you.
Where are you right now?
The call keeps dropping.
Well, you see...
I have something to tell you.
You do? I have something to tell you, too.
- Oh.
- Door opening.
By the way...
Where are you, honey? What?
Honey, where are you?
Well...
What are you doing here, honey?
You see...
It just happened, honey.
Dad.
You've grown so much.
Dad, what's with all these boxes?
Well...
Are you going somewhere?
Have you lost your mind?
A research assignment?
And in the countryside?
Why didn't you tell me this sooner?
You're the one to talk.
What are you doing here with
the kids without telling me?
I had my reasons.
Exactly. Why are the kids...
Ji Cheon. What are you doing here?
Mom told me to come.
I asked him to come to the airport.
We had a lot of luggage.
Exactly. So why?
Ji Sang...
was expelled.
What?
Expelled?
There was a fight among some kids...
It just happened.
Would you understand even if I told you?
What kind of fight was it
that you got expelled?
Seong Ji Sang. Come here right now!
You can scold him later.
Right now, you need to
figure out this situation.
You should've told me first
if something like this happened.
Did you ever answer your phone
when I called you?
When I called you back,
you never answered either.
I was trying to sort things out.
That's why.
(Moving Company)
For now, let's go.
Where exactly are we going?
We'll be there in the blink of an eye.
It's not too far from Seoul.
(Simwoo-myeon 157 km)
(Moving Day)
What?
A rural vacation?
This isn't the house.
I clearly...
showed him the pictures...
You rented a house
just by looking at pictures?
That's not it.
I think there's been a mistake.
What the...
Daddy.
Dad.
No one can live here.
Look. It's haunted.
Haunted?
Seriously?
No, Ji Gu. This...
Unbelievable.
I clearly asked for this house.
This one.
- It's not that.
- Stop.
You're here.
I thought you were coming alone,
but the whole family is here.
- Welcome to Yeonri-ri... What?
- Chief.
This isn't the house.
What's wrong?
Well, I...
I was talking about this house.
We looked at so many houses.
How would I know which house is which?
It's so hot.
How long are you going to keep looking?
You can take a look.
I won't do it anymore.
I won't do it. I won't.
What about this house?
Yes, that one is available.
They just got here from Canada.
How can they live in a place like this?
Actually, it's perfect.
That other house has
a broken water pipe right now.
There's no hot water either.
This is what we'll do.
You stay here for now.
When the repairs are done,
you can move there, okay?
This place is closer to
the Mat Story field anyway.
Sir.
Should we unload your stuff or not?
It's getting dark.
Are you going to make your family...
sleep in the yard tonight? Well?
Please unload everything.
He said to unload.
I'm sure the inside is okay.
Let's go, Ji Sang.
Be careful.
Ugh, dust.
Be careful, Ji Gu. Be careful.
Don't run. Don't run. It's dusty.
No.
No. Bugs! Bugs!
I'm going back.
I'm going back to Seoul.
No, no, no.
It's dangerous right now. It's nighttime.
I can clean this place up quickly.
I'll get rid of the cockroaches and...
Bugs.
A spider over there.
You're not supposed to kill spiders.
They say it brings bad luck.
Get lost. This is my room.
No, that's mine.
Mom.
Be quiet. I'm exhausted.
I can't share a room with him.
I need my own room.
Me too. He's so dirty.
He's always dropping snack crumbs.
You two. Come here.
Right now.
Come here.
That's not fair.
I want my own room!
As for the room...
You have to share a room.
If you don't want to...
Get out.
Dad.
Is your company bankrupt?
No.
I came here to do research.
Development. Yes.
Development.
My head.
Honey.
Be careful. Are you okay?
Goodness.
A little more.
No. Push. Push.
No, Ji Cheon. Pull it that way.
Push.
Don't push like that. Grab the top.
Grab the top. Grab the top.
You have to grab the top.
I'm sorry, but can you please help?
You don't have much stuff.
It'll be done soon.
You can't see anything once the sun sets.
Finish it up quickly. Come on.
Finish it up.
He's no help.
Slowly. Slowly. Slowly.
No.
Are you moving your stuff or
breaking the cart?
The first one, obviously.
Keep up the good work.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
It won't be delivered tomorrow.
I'm going crazy here.
Even in Canada, everything gets delivered.
How am I supposed to live here?
Was this always this big?
It...
By the way, the gas isn't connected.
Isn't the landlord coming? Where is he?
- Well...
- Here's the landlady.
(Deok Rae)
(Ok Rae)
(Mak Rae)
Is this a dining table
or a wooden platform?
Why is it so big?
The furniture doesn't match at all.
How chaotic.
Are you the landlady?
I'm Seong Tae Hun, the tenant.
Not me.
Her.
What about the gas?
You need to call the gas company.
Why are you looking for me?
Do you want me to fart instead?
Stop it, Ok Rae.
You need LPG.
Take out your phone.
This is the number you should call.
- Okay?
- Okay.
We came by to see how you were doing.
The whole family is here.
It's nice and lively.
Welcome.
Do you want me to fart for you?
Ok Rae. Let's go. Let's go.
(Moving Day)
I'll be washing the rice until tomorrow.
How am I supposed to cook
in a place like this?
Should we eat out today?
We must eat jajangmyeon on moving day.
Ji Sang. Ji Gu. It's been a while
since you had jajangmyeon, right?
Let's go.
This is jajangmyeon?
It's cooler now that the wind is blowing.
It's good.
Let's eat something even better soon.
There's no restaurant that delivers here.
I don't know
if we're eating kimchi for the ramyeon,
or the other way around.
It's good when you eat them
together, honey.
With this,
that kimchi goes really well.
Where am I?
I'll only stay for a few days.
When did you get here, honey?
If I left you alone
after seeing this mess,
I wouldn't be able to sleep. That's why.
Mom. Mom!
- What is it? What?
- A centipede.
Wow. A centipede. It's so gross.
It's so disgusting.
A centipede?
Ji Sang. Go get Ji Cheon,
and close the door behind you.
No. You go close it.
Go now. Go.
Go close the door now.
But it's so gross.
I think my whole body is itchy.
Maybe we should just sleep here
for tonight.
Dad.
- Yes?
- Wake up.
Mom.
Yes?
I'm scared.
Ji Gu, you're scared?
I'm scared because all the lights are off.
It kind of feels like we're camping.
Actually,
they say the countryside is much better
for people than the city.
There's phytoncide from the trees,
the smell of grass calms your nerves,
and since there's no noise pollution,
your body produces more melatonin
so you can sleep deeper.
Yes, but...
we should sleep at night, right?
Okay.
But I'm scared.
Let's just hang in there a little longer.
But I don't want to.
Good night.
Oh, my God.
I can't sleep.
I'll be up all night.
You three.
You've all grown so much.
Why doesn't this key go in?
Darn.
(Mat Story Yeonri-ri Branch)
What are you doing?
Who are you? Who?
Do people in this town
enjoy scaring others?
Since yesterday...
It's open.
Are you the building manager?
Or a Mat Story employee?
You'll be able to open most things.
Wait. Wait...
So you think I'm the outcast
they sent down here?
You can look down on me all you want.
(Napa cabbage research fully suspended)
How am I supposed to research
napa cabbage in a place like this?
Napa cabbage research fully suspended?
I want to go back to Seoul.
I'm going to kill Director Choi.
All you Mat Story jerks.
You abandoned me?
Me?
(2016 Work Log)
The soil has been neglected
for a long time,
so drainage and nutrients are
completely imbalanced.
All professional staff
need to be deployed.
The site selection was a failure.
What's going to happen now?
Do nothing.
Nothing.
Headquarters has abandoned Yeonri-ri.
Do nothing.
Headquarters...
has abandoned Yeonri-ri.
Why won't this start?
Why won't it?
This is his first day at work.
It's hot.
Air conditioner...
Come on.
Is it jet lag? I'm dying.
It's hot.
If you're hot, why are you wrapped up
in a blanket?
Goodness. Look at all this sweat.
Goodness.
What?
Dr. Seong?
Dr. Seong.
(Yeonri-ri Village)
This is nice.
Son, where are you?
You need to eat lunch.
Move out of the way.
Don't use your phone while you're walking.
Or you'll get hurt.
I should go back now.
What's that? Is that a snail?
What is he doing in the rice field?
Your clothes are dirty already.
Come with us.
Me?
Who else is there?
Are we allowed to take him with us?
He's with that Mat Story family
that caused all that fuss.
Mat Story or whatever,
we're short on workers.
Making a guy who's doing nothing
work won't kill him.
Let's go.
Together.
It smells amazing in here.
Hey.
Looks like a great harvest this year.
Look at them hanging everywhere.
My goodness.
These cucumbers are smooth
and handsome, just like me.
Go on in.
Wow.
Close your mouth before a fly goes in.
You've never seen a cucumber field before?
No, I've never seen a cucumber field
like this.
Here.
Take this and start from over there.
Pick as you go.
Look.
Like this. Like this.
If you don't fill this basket,
you won't get paid today.
Okay.
What? Wait.
I've never done this kind of work before.
You think I was born
picking cucumbers then?
Do it before I smack you.
I'll try.
When am I going to organize all this?
First, I'll put away the blankets.
Stationery...
There.
Come on.
My phone.
I need to call Carol.
Mom.
We're going back to Seoul, right?
Or let's go back to Toronto. Please?
What would you even do in Toronto?
Carol says she misses me.
I even have money to buy a plane ticket.
So let's go back.
Is anyone home?
Hello?
Yes?
Who are you?
Hi.
You're from Seoul, right?
Can I help you?
Well...
She's the head
of the Yeonri-ri Women's Association.
She also runs a cafe in town,
and a hair salon.
She's the big shot of Yeonri-ri.
I'm not a big shot.
I'm Nam Hye Sun.
I live right across from you.
I see.
It's nice to meet you.
So when are you planning to
go back to Seoul?
My husband will go back
after he finishes his work.
But I might go back sooner.
Those people from Mat Story...
Did they last two months?
No.
The longest lasted a month and a half.
Oh.
If you're planning to stay for
more than a year,
you'll have to join
the Women's Association.
I'm sorry.
I think we'll be going back before then.
Is that so?
All right then.
- Let's go.
She didn't even offer us a glass of water.
That's just wrong.
Forget it.
It's not like we don't have
water to drink.
If you say that, people will say
we're hazing her.
This is upsetting.
Unbelievable.
This is real hazing.
It doesn't look that difficult.
Do I just pick it?
Ow, that hurts.
What? How am I supposed to do this?
It hurts so much.
What was that?
Something just went past me.
What?
Ma'am.
How do you pick them so easily?
Did she not hear me?
Ma'am. I'll come over to your side.
Ma'am.
A hearing aid.
I guess you can't hear very well.
I'll watch and learn from you.
I'm sorry.
Who?
You're the scooter girl from earlier.
Oh.
He's from the family that moved here
from Seoul.
And this girl...
She lives next door to yours.
You two are neighbors.
The phone guy.
So what happened to your clothes?
Well...
He looked bored, rolling around
in the field. So we brought him here.
Hey, tall boy. You know what'll happen
if you don't fill that basket, right?
I'll smack you.
I can do a good job.
I'll do my best.
Ow.
- He's useless.
- Goodness.
You've clearly never touched dirt
in your whole life.
Are you a student?
Yes, I'm a college student.
I came down here for a bit with my dad.
A college student came here with his dad.
You're a good son.
I'm only staying a few days.
Oh. I'm Im Bo Mi.
I'm a nutritionist at a school here.
I come and help out in the fields
like this when I have free time.
I'm Seong Ji Cheon.
Right here.
You have to grab the top part here.
Cucumber thorns are sharp,
so even with gloves, it hurts
if you grab too hard.
Like this?
Like this. Like this.
This is where the future begins.
Seong Tae Hun napa cabbage.
Kimchi made
from multi-functional cabbage...
that tastes good and
has anti-cancer properties.
(Napa cabbage variety development
fully suspended)
(Seedling greenhouse)
(Yeonri-ri Project)
Farming isn't complicated.
All I need is land, seeds, and water.
I have everything here.
If you plant it, it'll grow.
Why isn't this working? Why?
Why won't it work? Why? Why? Why?
It's working. It's working.
It's working.
It's working. It's working. It's working.
Yes. I can do this.
I will go back to Seoul...
with my wife and kids!
I'm going back.
You seem full of energy.
What are you doing here?
Chief. I'm farming.
This isn't even your own plot.
You got demoted so this is your hobby now?
I wasn't demoted.
I understand why you think that,
but I came here to develop napa cabbage...
that only Mat Story can produce.
Napa cabbage?
Napa cabbage farming?
Yes.
Napa cabbage with consistent sugar levels,
and specialized nutrients,
grown organically,
and made into a specialty product
of Yeonri-ri...
So Mat Story napa cabbage will
become a local specialty?
Yes, exactly.
I'll call it Seong Tae Hun cabbage...
Have...
Have some shame.
You're basically a slave
to a big corporation, aren't you?
Chief.
That's a bit harsh, don't you think?
Harsh?
You showed up looking like a beggar
in this heat,
so I even helped you find a house,
and now listen to the nonsense
you're spouting.
I was going to let it go because
I made mistakes, too,
but do you even have
a real estate license?
Showing houses without a license...
is fraud.
A real estate license?
I'm glad you mentioned it.
What about you?
Do you have a farming license?
Why would I need a license to farm?
Yes, you do.
Because farming is something
done by people.
But Mat Story isn't people.
It's a beast that killed this land.
How can you say this land is dead?
You left this fine land abandoned for
ten years and killed it.
Clear away the rocks if you want.
See if a blade of grass will grow.
I used to be a researcher.
I know what to do.
No, you don't.
I'll make sure you can't do anything here.
That's ridiculous.
How can you possibly do that?
Tell me.
What do you think...
you can do on your own here...
without me?
Village...
chief!
Like being struck by lightning
and splashed with water.
Yes.
That could happen in life.
It happens.
But why does it have to be me?
(We thank Min Sung Wuk
for his special appearance)
(Cabbage Your Life)
Send 1,500 seedling samples
within a month.
Why won't it grow? Why?
Mr. Seong Ji Cheon.
I'm Officer Park Soon Kyung.
Easy to remember, right?
I officially declare this
as the village chief.
Do not help Seong Tae Hun at all.
Village chief's official stamp.
Get a recommendation from
the village chief.
Village chief. Village chief.
Village chief.
I'll deal with
the Women's Association first.
Hello.
Let's find a way.
If there's no proper way,
I'll find another way.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)